A Guide to the David Rockefeller papers, Photographic collections, Numbered Albums FA1316
Rockefeller Archive Center
- DR and Geoff Morse Trips and Events, 2006-2008; Image quality varies. (Box 237)
  DR traveled with Geoff Morse and others: Sailing trip in 2006 and Botswana safari trip in 2008. Images of baby christening as well, possibly of Morse's child.
  127 images.
- Celebration of DR's 85th Birthday and Laurance Rockefeller's 90th Birthday, Pocantico Hills, 2000 June 17 (Box 238)
  Family dinner held at the Playhouse in Pocantico Hills, New York, to celebrate DR's 85th and LSR's 90th birthdays.
- Compilation Album of Family Photos for DR's 75th Birthday, 1990 June; Some black-and-white images. (Box 239)
  Photos of family members from various branches compiled to celebrate DR's 75th birthday.
- Geneva Hayes Album, 2010 (Box 240)
  Family photo album.
- "Harvest Moon" Boat Trip, 1994 June-August (Box 241)
  DR and PR boat trip on the "Harvest Moon," taken in three parts: 1) Tarrytown to Sackett's Harbor, New York, on the Hudson River to Troy, then on the Erie Canal to Lake Oneida, and then on the Oswego Canal to Sackett's Harbor on Lake Ontario. 2) Sackett's Harbor, New York, to Burlington, Vermont, on the St. Lawrence River and Richilieu River to Lake Champlain, Vermont. Joined by Warren and Muriel Lindquist. 3) Burlington, Vermont, to Tarrytown, New York, on Lake Champlain to the Champlain Canal to the Hudson River
- Hudson Pines Carriage Rides, 2008, Some blurry images. (Box 242)
  DR carriage rides with friends and staff on Hudson Pines property and Rockefeller State Park in Pocantico Hills, New York.
- Jamaica Trip, Part 2, 2013 (Box 243)
  DR trip to Jamaica with friends and associates.
- London and Paris Trip, 2013, Most images are grainy. (Box 244)
  DR trip to London and Paris with friends and family members. Sightseeing, dining, and shopping.
- La Romana, Dominican Republic Trip, 2012, Image quality varies. (Box 245)
  DR vacation to La Romana in the Dominican Republic with staff and friends. Sailing, kayaking, hiking, swimming. A CD of the photos is included in the album.
- La Romana, Dominican Republic Trip, 2013, One black-and-white image. (Box 246)
  DR vacation to La Romana in Dominican Republic with staff and friends. Sailing, birthday celebration. A CD of the photos is included in the album.
  49 images.
- La Romana, Dominican Republic Trip, 2014 (Box 247)
  DR vacation to La Romana in Dominican Republic with staff and friends. Sailing, swimming, golfing, hiking, helicopter rides, gardens, dance performance, host's dog (Pele). A CD of the photos is included in the album.
  119 images.
- Morocco and Paris Trip, Part 2, 2014, Several images are grainy/blurry. (Box 248)
  DR trip to Morocco and Paris with staff and friends. Camel rides, mosques, Royal Palace in Fez, Sahara Desert, Notre Dame, Louvre, Eiffel Tower.
- Morocco Trip, 2008, Some images are grainy. (Box 249)
  DR trip to Morocco with staff members Marnie Pillsbury and Peter Johnson. Visits to Fez and Marrakesh. Camel rides, desert views, henna tattoos, and goats in trees.
- New York City Partnership Compilation Album to Honor David Rockefeller, 1980-1988; Black-and-white images. (Box 250)
  Compilation of images from DR's work with the New York City Partnership, particularly regarding housing and development. Upon DR's resignation from the board in 1988, the Partnership and the New York Chamber of Commerce established the David Rockefeller Fellow Program. Images of Mayor Ed Koch and Governor Mario Cuomo.
- Wyoming Trip, 1954 (Box 251)
  Boating and camping trip in Wyoming, probably the Grand Tetons, with family and friends.
- Australia and Papua New Guinea Trip, Part 2, 1981 (Box 252)
- Michael Lambert and Rebecca Rockefeller's Wedding, 2008 June 21; Some black-and-white images.; Some images are grainy. (Box 253)
  Photo album of wedding and related events.
  135 images.
- Paraguay Trip, 1994 (Box 254)
  DR and PR trip to Paraguay. Tours of industrial site and hydroelectric dam, agricultural sites, and historical Jesuit ruins of Trinidad (La Santisima Trinidad de Parana). Also, DR received a medal from President Juan Carlos Wasmosy and attended a formal dinner event.
  164 images.
- Paraguay Trip Part 1, 1994 (Box 255)
  DR and PR trip to Paraguay. This album contains additional images of tour of hydroelectric dam. See Box 254 for images of entire trip.
- Paraguay Trip Part 2, 1994 (Box 256)
  DR and PR trip to Paraguay. This album contains additional images of tour outside the hydroelectric dam and of the reception with President Wasmosy. See Box 254 for images of entire trip.
- Paraguay Trip Part 3, 1994 (Box 257)
  DR and PR trip to Paraguay. This album contains additional images of tour of the Jesuit ruins of Trinidad (La Santisima Trinidad de Parana). See Box 254 for images of entire trip.
- Peggy Rockefeller Highlights Compilation Album, 1950-1990; Some black-and-white images. (Box 258)
  Album of images of PR with friends and family members over several years. Likely compiled for her 75th birthday. Includes scenery at Hudson Pines home in Pocantico Hills, New York, and scenery on Buckle Island in Maine. Several images of Peggy sailing or on the farm with cows.
- Pocantico Hills Album on Celebration of 30th Anniversary of the Chase International Advisory Committee, 1995 October 29 (Box 259)
  DR and PR hosted a reception at Hudson Pines and a dinner at the Playhouse in Pocantico Hills for the Chase Manhattan Bank International Advisory Committee, which DR chaired at the time. Attendees included Henry Kissinger, Nancy Kissinger, Gustavo Cisneros, Tom Labrecque, and Sheila Lebrecque.
- Quattrone Family Album, 2014 (Box 260)
  92 images.
- San Juan Islands, Washington Trip, 1992 (Box 261)
  DR and PR trip in the San Juan Islands with friends. Includes sailing, garden walks, and hiking, plus excursions to Victoria, British Columbia.
  95 images.
- Southern India Trip, 2004 (Box 262)
  DR trip to southern India with family and friends: sightseeing, ruins, temples, monkeys, crafts, elephant rides, visit to a tea estate.
- Thailand Cruise, 2009 (Box 263)
  DR sailing trip in Thailand with grandchildren. During the trip, DR had an audience with King Bhumibol Adulyadej.
- Valerie Rockefeller and James Carnegie Wedding Album, 2000 May; Some black-and-white images. (Box 264)
  Wedding album of DR's niece, Valerie. Held in the National Cathedral in Washington, DC.
- Little Long Pond Event, Mt. Desert Island, Maine, 2015 (Box 265)
  DR attended an event held at Little Long Pond and adjacent gardens on Mount Desert Island, Seal Harbor, Maine.
  21 images.
- Neva and DR Family Album, 2013 (Box 266)
  DR and Neva Goodwin with family members in Maine. Some images at the Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden in Seal Harbor.
  36 images.
- Quattrone Family Album, 2011, Image quality varies. (Box 267)
- Quattrone Family Album, 2010, Some black-and-white images. (Box 268)
- Annette de la Renta's Dinner for DR's 100th Birthday, 2015; Some grainy images. (Box 269)
  Annette de la Renta hosted a dinner party to honor DR on his 100th birthday. Guests include Henry Kissinger, Nancy Kissinger, Michael Bloomberg, Charlie Rose, Diana Taylor, Alice Victor, and Marnie Pillsbury.
  14 images
- Morocco Trip, Part 1, 1983, 1983 February; Black-and-white images. (Box 270)
  DR and PR trip to Morocco with friends Robert Douglass, Linda Douglass, J. Richardson Dilworth, Elizabeth Dilworth, and Joseph Reed. DR had an audience with King Hassan II and later a meeting with Prime Minister Maati Bouabid.
- Air Staff Album, 2015; Some images are low quality or grainy. (Box 271)
  Employees on DR's planes. Likely compiled on the occasion of DR's 100th birthday.
  20 images
- Compilation Album for DR's 85th Birthday, 1985-2000 (Box 272)
  Photos from various years were compiled by his staff as a gift for DR's 85th birthday in 2000. The images are mostly of staff and friends in social settings.
  56 images
- Dedication of the John D. Rockefeller Jr. Library, Brown University, 1964 November 16; Black-and-white images. (Box 273)
  Album of the dedication ceremony of the new John D. Rockefeller Jr. Library on the campus of Brown University in Providence, Rhode Island. It was JDR Jr's alma mater, and he provided substantial financial support to the school during his lifetime. David, Peggy, and Martha Baird Rockefeller all attended the event, and David spoke during the ceremony. Martha unveiled the plaque. The album includes quotes from the various speeches made.
- Africa Trip, Part 1, 1971, Black-and-white images. (Box 274)
  DR's trip to 8 countries on behalf of Chase Manhattan Bank: Ethiopia, Kenya, Tanzania, Zambia, Congo, Nigeria, Cote d'Ivoire (Ivory Coast), and Liberia. Images taken by Joseph Reed. DR met with 6 heads of state. Tours of all countries and a safari.
- Africa Trip, Part 2, 1971, Black-and-white images. (Box 275)
  DR's trip to 4 countries on behalf of Chase Manhattan Bank: Congo, Zaire, Zambia, and Tanzania. Images taken by Joseph Reed. Tours of each country, showing the local residents, landscape, and area wildlife.
- Tour of Beijing Tile Factory (Box 276)
  Images of the process of creating tiles. DR does not appear in these photos.
  26 images
- Quattrone Family Album, 2013, Image quality varies. (Box 277)
  82 images.
- Barry Walker Compilation Album of DR Family (Box 278)
  Photos with DR family, including homes in Maine and Pocantico Hills, New York. Travel in several countries.
  84 images
- Slides of Hudson Pines Horses, 1950 (Box 279)
  DR and PR's horses at Hudson Pines, their home in Pocantico Hills, New York.
- Golden's Bridge Horse Show Slides, 1951 (Box 279)
  Members of DR and PR's family competed in a horse show held at Golden's Bridge in New York.
- Hudson Pines Slides, 1954 (Box 279)
  DR and PR's family at Hudson Pines, their home in Pocantico Hills, New York.
- Hudson Pines Slides, 1960 (Box 279)
- Abby Rockefeller's Graduation Slides, 1961 (Box 279)
- Hudson Pines Slides, 1961 (Box 279)
- Family Portrait Slides, 1962 (Box 279)
  Portraits of DR and PR's family.
- Hudson Pines Slides, 1962 (Box 279)
- Hudson Pines Slides, 1963 (Box 279)
- David Rockefeller Jr.'s Graduation Slides, 1963 (Box 279)
  Images from David Jr's graduation from Cambridge.
- Hudson Pines Slides, 1964 (Box 279)
- Slides of Horses at Hudson Pines Farm, 1965 (Box 279)
  Images of DR and PR's horses at Hudson Pines Farm in Pocantio Hills, New York.
- Hudson Pines Slides, 1968 (Box 279)
- Hudson Pines Slides, 1947 (Box 279)
  DR and PR's family and horses at Hudson Pines, their home in Pocantico Hills, New York.
- Slides of Hudson Pines Cattle, 1977 (Box 279)
  Images of cattle/bulls raised and sold at by Hudson Pines Farms, DR and PR's property in Pocantico Hills, New York (2 sets).
- Newfoundland, Canada Trip Slides, 1962 August (Box 279)
  DR and PR's trip sailing around Newfoundland with family.
- Buckle Island, Maine Trip Slides, 1963 (Box 279)
  DR and PR trip with family to Buckle Island, Maine.
- Seal Harbor, Maine Trip Slides, 1954 (Box 279)
  DR and PR's visit with family to their home in Seal Harbor, Maine.
- Seal Harbor, Maine Trip Slides, 1965 (Box 279)
  DR and PR's visit with family to their home in Seal Harbor, Maine (2 sets).
- Seal Harbor, Maine Trip Slides, 1968 (Box 279)
  DR and PR's visit to their home in Seal Harbor, Maine. Mostly images of the Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden.
- Sailing in Seal Harbor, Maine Trip Slides, 1973 (Box 279)
  DR and PR's visit with family to their home in Seal Harbor, Maine. Mostly images of sailing.
- Richard and Nancy Rockefeller Wedding Slides, 1974 (Box 279)
  DR and PR attended son Richard's wedding.
- Seal Harbor, Maine Trip Slides, 1978 (Box 279)
- St. Bart's Trip Slides, 1958 (Box 279)
  DR and PR's visit with family to Colombier, their home on St. Bart's, in the Caribbean.
- West Indies (?) Trip Slides, 1960, 1960 January (Box 279)
  DR and PR trip with family and the Puseys, possibly in the West Indies.
- St. Bart's Trip Slides, 1961 (Box 279)
- St. Bart's Construction Slides, 1963, 1963 July (Box 279)
  Construction of the guest house, Teepee, at DR and PR's home on St. Bart's, in the Caribbean.
- St. Bart's Trip Slides, 1964 (Box 279)
- St. Croix Trip Slides, 1964, 1964 August (Box 279)
  DR and PR trip to St. Croix with friends.
- David Rockefeller Family Portraits, 1955-1956, Black-and-white images. (Box 280)
  Album of duplicate prints of family images taken mostly in 1956 at DR and PR's home Hudson Pines, in Pocantico Hills, New York. One image is from 1955. Includes images with examples from DR's beetle collection. Because these are duplicates, they were not scanned. See Box 3 for scanned files.
  17 images.
- Morocco Trip, 1972 (Box 281)
  DR and PR trip to Morocco. Images by Joseph Reed. Camel rides. Scenes of villages and wildllife.
- Italy Trip Slides, 1951 (Box 282)
  DR trip to Italy.
- Bangkok, Thailand and Isfahan, Iran Trip Slides, 1962 (Box 282)
  DR trip to Thailand. Trip to Isfahan, Iran.
- Scotland and France Trip Slides, 1961 (Box 282)
  DR and PR trip to Scotland and France.
- Tarrytown Slides, 1961 (Box 282)
  Images at DR and PR's home in Pocantico Hills, New York (also referred to as Tarrytown).
- Ringing Point Construction Slides, 1972 (Box 282)
  Images of the construction of Ringing Point, DR and PR's home in Seal Harbor, Maine.
- Damascus, Syria and Kuwait Trip Slides, 1953 (Box 282)
  DR trip to Damascus, Syria and to Kuwait.
- Buella Island, Maine Trip Slides, 1966, 1966 September (Box 282)
  DR and PR trip to Buella Island in Maine.
- Slides of DR and PR's Children, 1970s-Early 1980s, 1970s-1980s (Box 282)
  Photo shoot of DR and PR's children. Individual and group images.
- St. Bart's Construction Slides, 1958 (Box 282)
  Construction images of DR and PR's home Colombier, on St. Bart's, in the Caribbean.
- Rockefeller "Roadshow" Slides, 1972 (Box 282)
  Compilation of images of DR and PR's family from various trips in 1972.
- Abby's Graduation Slides, 1961 (Box 282)
  DR and PR's trip to attend daughter Abby's graduation.
- Mexico Trip Slides, 1946 (Box 282)
  DR and PR trip to Mexico.
- Bolivia, Peru, and Ecuador Trip Slides, 1950 (Box 282)
  DR and PR trip to Bolivia, Peru, and Ecuador.
- The Eyrie, Seal Harbor, Maine Trip Slides, 1972 (Box 282)
  Contemporaneous images of the exterior of The Eyrie, former home of John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller in Seal Harbor, Maine. Also images of the Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden and other sites in Seal Harbor. Includes winter scenes, which are less common of the Maine properties.
- Wyoming Trip Slides, 1960 (Box 282)
  DR and PR trip to the JY Ranch in Jackson Hole, Wyoming.
- Arizona and Jackson Hole, Wyoming Trip Slides, 1942 (Box 282)
  DR and PR trip to Arizona and to the JY Ranch in Jackson Hole, Wyoming.
- Morocco Trip Slides, 1972 (Box 282)
  DR trip to Morocco.
- Bali Trip Slides, 1971 (Box 282)
  DR trip to Bali.
- JY Ranch, Wyoming Trip Slides, 1960 (Box 282)
- St. Bart's Trip Slides, 1962, 1962 Christmas (Box 282)
  DR and PR celebrate Christmas with their family at Colombier, their home on St. Bart's, in the Caribbean.
- Morocco Trip Slides, 1972 (Box 282)
  Images of DR trip to Morocco (2 sets).
- Nepal Trip Slides, 1971 (Box 282)
  Images of DR trip to Nepal (2 sets).
- Bangkok, Thailand Trip Slides, 1962 (Box 282)
  Images of DR trip to Bangkok, Thailand (2 sets).
- Family Portraits, 1940-1950, Black-and-white images. (Box 283)
  Formal portraits of PR and five of her children. Also Koshiba portrait of Abby Aldrich Rockefeller.
- Harvard University compilation album for DR's 101st Birthday, 2016; Some black-and-white images. (Box 284)
  A commemorative album of a few images of Harvard and DR compiled for DR's 101st birthday.
- Compilation of Snapshots, 1944-2003; Mostly black-and-white images. (Box 285)
  Variety of snapshots (not in an album) either taken of DR or by DR. Earliest images are from DR's service in World War II, mostly from his travels in Syria, Algeria, and Egypt. Other images are of his family on vacation in the 1940s through the 1960s, likely in Wyoming, the Caribbean, and Maine. One image is of DR and Nelson Mandela, probably taken during DR's 1995 trip to South Africa on behalf of Chase Manhattan Bank's international program.
- Netherlands Trip, 2008, 2008 November (Box 286)
  DR trip with staff to the Netherlands for the annual Bilderberg Conference. They visited the Hague and Amsterdam, as well as Paris on the return trip.
- Family Portraits I, Some black-and-white images. (Box 287)
  Portraits of 3 of DR's children.
  9 images.
- Family Portraits II, Black-and-white images. (Box 288)
- Family Portraits (2 copies), 1944-1945; Black-and-white images. (Box 289)
  Photos of Peggy and three of her children from 1945 (two copies). The 1944 album with two of her children was not scanned.
- Portraits of David Rockefeller and Siblings, 1940s; Black-and-white images. (Box 290)
  Photos of the 6 siblings during World War II: Abby, John 3rd, Nelson, Laurance, Winthrop, and David.
  7 images.
- St. Bart's Trip Slides, 1962 (Box 291)
  DR and PR trip to Colombier, their home on St. Bart's, in the Caribbean.
- Hong Kong Trip Slides, 1962 (Box 291)
  DR trip to Hong Kong.
- Iran Trip Slides, 1986 (Box 291)
  DR trip to Iran.
- Iran Trip Slides, 1982 (Box 291)
- Cambodia Trip Slides, 1962 (Box 291)
  DR trip to Cambodia, including Angkor Wat temple.
- Saudi Arabia Trip Slides, 1962 (Box 291)
  DR trip to Jeddah, Saudi Arabia.
- Japan Trip Slides, 1962 (Box 291)
  DR trip to Japan.
- Korea Trip Slides, 1971 (Box 291)
  DR trip to Korea.
- Eyrie and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden, Seal Harbor, Maine, Trip Slides, Part 2, 1960 (Box 291)
  DR and PR visit to Seal Harbor, Maine, to his parents' home, The Eyrie, before it was torn down. Also visited the Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden.
- Eyrie and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden, Seal Harbor, Maine, Trip Slides, Part 1, 1960 (Box 291)
- Africa Trip Slides, 1959 (Box 291)
  DR trip to several African nations.
- California Trip Slides, 1952 (Box 291)
  DR trip to California.
- Saudi Arabia and Egypt Trip Slides, 1953 (Box 291)
- Hudson Pines Slides, 1949-1952 (Box 291)
  Images of Hudson Pines, DR and PR's home in Pocantico Hills, New York.
- St. Bart's Trip Slides, c.1957 (Box 291)
  DR and PR trip to St. Bart's, in the Caribbean.
- Kenya and Ethiopia Trip Slides, 1959 (Box 291)
  DR trip to Kenya and to Ethiopia.
- Hudson Pines Slides, 1958 (Box 291)
- St. Bart's Trip Slides, 1962 (Box 291)
- St. Bart's Trip Slides, 1959 (Box 291)
  DR and PR's home, Colombier, on St. Bart's, in the Caribbean.
- Big Sur, California Trip Slides, 1961 (Box 291)
  DR trip to Big Sur.
- Hudson Pines Slides, 1954 (Box 291)
- Seal Harbor, Maine Trip Slides, 1954, Part 1 (Box 291)
  DR and PR trip to Seal Harbor, Maine.
- Seal Harbor, Maine Trip Slides, 1954, Part 2 (Box 291)
- Colonial Williamsburg Trip Slides, 1954 (Box 291)
  DR and PR trip to Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia.
- St. Bart's Trip Slides, 1973 (Box 292)
- JY Ranch, Wyoming Trip Slides, Undated (Box 292)
  DR and PR trip to JY Ranch in Wyoming.
- JY Ranch, Wyoming Trip Slides, 1964 (Box 292)
- Vail, Colorado Trip Slides, 1968 (Box 292)
  DR and PR trip to Vail, Colorado.
- Greece and Crete Trip Slides, 1959 (Box 292)
  DR trip to Greece and to Crete.
- Kenya, Zimbabwe, and South Africa Trip Slides, 1959 (Box 292)
  Part of DR trip to seven African nations, he visited Kenya, Victoria Falls in Zimbabwe (then Rhodesia), and Kruger National Park in South Africa.
- Ghana and Congo Trip Slides, 1959 (Box 292)
  As part of a trip to seven African nations, DR visited Accra, Ghana, and Kinshasa (formerly Leopoldville) in the Congo (then Belgian Congo).
- St. Bart's Trip Slides, 1968 (Box 292)
- France Trip Slides, 1961 (Box 292)
- Venezuela Trip Slides, 1962, 1962 September (Box 292)
  DR trip to Venezuela, including a visit Ciudad Bolivar and to brother Nelson's ranch, Monte Sacro.
- Venezuela Trip Slides, 1948 (Box 292)
  DR trip to Venezuela.
- Cuba Trip Slides, 1948 (Box 292)
  DR trip to Cuba.
- Puerto Rico Trip Slides, 1948 (Box 292)
  DR trip to Puerto Rico.
- Peru Trip Slides, 1950 (Box 292)
  DR trip to Peru.
- England and France Trip Slides, 1951 (Box 292)
  DR and PR trip to England and to France.
- Panama Trip Slides, 1951 (Box 292)
  DR trip to Panama.
- Greece and Crete Trip Slides, 1959 (Box 292)
  DR and PR trip to Greece and to Crete.
- Scotland and England Trip Slides, 1961 (Box 292)
  DR and PR trip to Scotland and to England with family members.
  Material related to living members of the Rockefeller Family is restricted.
- Rhone River Trip Slides, 1961 (Box 292)
  DR an PR trip to along the Rhone River.
- Afghanistan Trip Slides, 1963 (Box 292)
  DR trip to Afghanistan.
- India Trip Slides, 1963 (Box 292)
  DR trip to India (2 sets).
- World Trip Slides, 1971 (Box 292)
  DR and PR trip to various countries.
- Kenya Trip Slides, 1971 (Box 292)
  DR trip to Kenya.
- Bali Trip Slides, 1971 (Box 292)
- Egypt Trip Slides, 1971 (Box 292)
  DR trip to Egypt.
- Interior Images of Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research, 1950s; Black-and-white images. (Box 293)
  Interiors of rooms and common areas on the campus of the RIMR prior to its renaming in 1965 to Rockefeller University.
- Quattrone Family Album, 2016 (Box 294)
  Compilation album for DR from grandson Michael Quattrone and his family, likely from 2016.
- David and Peggy Rockefeller's Honeymoon Album, 1941; Black-and-white images. (Box 295)
  Images of David and Peggy on their honeymoon trip to JY Ranch in Jackson Hole, Wyoming: horseback riding, hunting, and camping.
- 100 Years of David Rockefeller Compilation Album, 2015 June 12; Some images are coming loose from their respective pages. (Box 296)
  An album of snapshots and handwritten messages compiled during the week of DR's 100th birthday by his grandson. Images are of the multiple generations of family members who attended his birthday celebration in Pocantico Hills, New York.
- Africa Trip, Part 4, 1971, Black-and-white images. (Box 297)
  DR trip to the Ivory Coast (Cote d'Ivoire) and Liberia on behalf of Chase Manhattan Bank. Images taken by Joseph Reed. DR met with Ivory Coast's first president, Felix Houphouet-Boigny, and Henry Konan Bedie, who later became president. Tours of the area and performances by local dance troupes. Tour of executive mansion and Chase Manhattan Bank branch in Monrovia, Liberia. The last few images appear to be taken in Maine with PR after DR returned.
- Africa Trip, 1973, Mostly black-and-white images. (Box 298)
  DR trip to Africa on behalf of Chase Manhattan Bank, including stops in Botswana, Cameroon, Egypt, Malawi, Senegal, and South Africa. Image taken by Joseph Reed. DR met with Cameroon's first president, Ahmadou Ahidjo, and also with Egyptian diplomat Ashraf Ghorbal, Malawi politician J.Z.U. Tembo, Senegalese poet Leopold Senghor, and South Africa state president Nicolaas Diederich. Tours of each country.
- World Trip, 1974, Black-and-white images. (Box 299)
  DR and PR trip to Philippines, Thailand, India, and Pakistan on behalf of Chase Manhattan Bank. Images by Joseph Reed. DR met with Philippines president Ferdinand Marcos and his wife, Imelda. They also visited the Raymond Magsaysay Center in Manila. In India, they visited the Taj Mahal and sailed along the Ganges River. DR met with business leader/philanthropist Ratan Naval Tata. In Pakistan, DR met with U.S. Ambassador Henry A. Byroade.
- Europe Trip, 1979, 1979 September; Mostly black-and-white images. (Box 300)
  DR trip to various European countries on behalf of Chase Manhattan Bank, including Yugoslavia, Italy, and Germany.
- China Trip, 1973, Mostly black-and-white images. (Box 301)